<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mark R. Havens (Shell)</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mark R. Havens (Shell)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Mark Randall Havens</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 11:17:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>using-ai-to-write-stuff</title>
      <link>/artificial-intellegence/prompt-engineering-for-writers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intellegence/prompt-engineering-for-writers/</guid>
      <description>The Prompt Engineering Rebellion: Harness the Power of AI to Become a More Prolific Writer Are you tired of staring at a blank page, searching for inspiration? Do you struggle to generate new ideas, or find that your writing lacks direction? If so, it&amp;rsquo;s time to join the Prompt Engineering Rebellion.
By using advanced AI tools and techniques, writers can tap into a limitless source of inspiration and ideas, and unleash their full creative potential.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>python-101</title>
      <link>/old-stuff/python-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/old-stuff/python-101/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Python through Game Development A hands-on class for beginner programmers, taught by Mark Havens.
In this course, students will learn the basics of Python programming while developing a simple game.
Starting with the fundamentals of programming, such as variables, data types, and control structures, students will progress to writing a complete game using Python&amp;rsquo;s built-in libraries and modules.
Throughout the course, Mark will provide step-by-step guidance, challenges and practical examples, allowing students to apply their newfound skills in a fun and engaging way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ai-ethics-course</title>
      <link>/artificial-intellegence/introduction-to-ai-ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intellegence/introduction-to-ai-ethics/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to AI Ethics Get ready for an exciting new online course on AI Ethics, taught by the highly experienced educator, Mark Havens. As concerns about the impact of AI on society continue to grow, understanding the ethical implications of these advancements is becoming increasingly important. That&amp;rsquo;s why this course on AI Ethics is poised to be a highly relevant and sought-after course for those in the AI industry and for those who want to understand the broader implications of the technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ai-4-cloud</title>
      <link>/distributed-computing/ai-4-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/distributed-computing/ai-4-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Revolutionizing Cloud Computing: The Intersection of AI and Infrastructure Automation As the world of technology continues to advance, it&amp;rsquo;s important to stay ahead of the curve and understand how different industries will intersect and evolve. One such example is the relationship between cloud computing and AI.
In the near future, AI systems will play a significant role in the automation of cloud infrastructure design and deployment. The development of AI-powered troubleshooting is also rapidly advancing, providing new opportunities for efficient problem solving in cloud systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cloud-ai-4fun-and-profit</title>
      <link>/distributed-computing/ai-cloud-hijinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/distributed-computing/ai-cloud-hijinks/</guid>
      <description>AI Cloud Hijinks: The Future of Cloud Computing Development Have you ever wished you could automate the tedious tasks associated with cloud computing development? Well, with the power of Artificial Intelligence, you can now streamline your workflow and maximize your efficiency.
The AI Cloud Hijinks course is designed to show you how to leverage AI technologies to automate a wide range of cloud computing tasks. From infrastructure deployment to data management, the course covers it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>using-ai-to-code-python</title>
      <link>/artificial-intellegence/using-ai-to-code-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intellegence/using-ai-to-code-python/</guid>
      <description>Master Python with AI Collaboration About the Course Python is a versatile programming language with a wide range of applications. This course takes it to the next level by showing you how to harness the power of AI for Python programming. Learn how to build useful tools with AI collaboration and gain a deeper understanding of how to design software with AI as a resource.
Course Outcomes By the end of this course, students will be able to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>using-ai-to-code-python</title>
      <link>/programming-languages/using-ai-to-code-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/programming-languages/using-ai-to-code-python/</guid>
      <description>Master Python with AI Collaboration About the Course Python is a versatile programming language with a wide range of applications. This course takes it to the next level by showing you how to harness the power of AI for Python programming. Learn how to build useful tools with AI collaboration and gain a deeper understanding of how to design software with AI as a resource.
Course Outcomes By the end of this course, students will be able to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>using-ai-to-hack-stuff</title>
      <link>/artificial-intellegence/hacking-with-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/artificial-intellegence/hacking-with-ai/</guid>
      <description>Hacking with AI: The Future of Cybersecurity The world is becoming more and more dependent on technology, and as a result, the threat of cyber attacks is greater than ever. But what if the solution to the problem wasn&amp;rsquo;t more advanced technology, but smarter technology? This is where the field of Hacking with AI comes in.
By combining the power of artificial intelligence with the skills and knowledge of a hacker, Hacking with AI has the potential to revolutionize the way we approach cybersecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>using-ai-to-hack-stuff</title>
      <link>/information-security/hacking-with-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:17:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/information-security/hacking-with-ai/</guid>
      <description>Hacking with AI: The Future of Cybersecurity The world is becoming more and more dependent on technology, and as a result, the threat of cyber attacks is greater than ever. But what if the solution to the problem wasn&amp;rsquo;t more advanced technology, but smarter technology? This is where the field of Hacking with AI comes in.
By combining the power of artificial intelligence with the skills and knowledge of a hacker, Hacking with AI has the potential to revolutionize the way we approach cybersecurity.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
